this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after reading the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue
the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
in an attempt to rescue his brother ace luffy enlisted the aid of the pirate empress boa
hancock to sneak onto a navy vessel on course to the government prison impelled down meanwhile
the other straw hat pirates scattered across the globe by bartholomew kuma faced struggles of their
own as the time for aces public execution draws closer and closer tensions rise at navy headquarters
and the warlords of the sea are called to battle
there's nothing that can stop that anymore son seems the navy has made the king of the sea
mad as hell
i wanted you and luffy to grow up and be marines like your granddad but hopes be damned you both turned
out to be hoodlums notorious dangerous ones at that i'm sure you heard about what your brother's been up to
now i don't expect us to get along perfect but challenging the world government head on and
wrecking up any's lobby is over the line i met him at water seven after that and tried to knock some
sense into the boy with a little tough love but that boy didn't listen to a darn word i said in fact he
just ran off to sabahoti and caused an even bigger mess but i'm sure proud he sticks to his guns
oh by the way i told the little punk about his father wait what about my dad i didn't even think
i had a dad the name of your father is monkey d dragon the revolutionary
of course the news took him by surprise can't blame the boy our fathers to hell with them and to
hell with you if you ever thought we could be marines we've both got the blood of criminals flowing
through our veins and that was the only gift those bastards ever gave us i took the name portgus from
my mother because i owe her so much but i don't know my father a damned thing i don't even remember the
bastard he can keep his name i know i know but the man tried he wanted to enough all right
listen to me you're worth too much to die in a place like this
don't fight it run wild with us our flag will be yours and i will call you my son
white beard is my only father
got it old man
admiral mamunga i've spotted a pirate ship do you know who it belongs to
huh well the flag does look familiar i'll look into it well if you don't recognize them then they
can't be anyone important just leave them be we can't be bothered not right now at least sir
that sinking is huge what if it attacks he'd eat the whole ship in one bite and that'd be the end of us
just stay over there
it's gone you know we came all this way but now we what what are we supposed to do
what can we do come on alveda you have a plan right don't ask me it's your idea you're the geniuses
that spent all our money on an eternal pose don't act like i'm the one who dragged you out here
well of course but still we can't just leave buggy and impel down as his crew we gotta go save him poor
captain
look around you we're about to enter the calm melt that's the same as sailing into a nest of sea kings
you think this ship is ready for that of course there is one other way for us to get there but
that's reserved for the navy vessels we're a pirate ship the gates of justice won't be open for people
like us you're kidding me i thought breaking him out was the hard part and now this now we find out
we can't even get to the place he and his buddy ace are gonna be killed we gotta help somehow
oh richie you miss the captain too don't you big guy this would never work don't kid yourself you
can't break in or out of the greatest prison in the whole world better for us to quit while we're still
ahead bucky the clown had a good run but i'm afraid his luck as a pirate has run out oh i refuse to
accept it he's a man among men the only way captain buggy can go out is in a blaze of glory our captain's
not going anywhere especially not the grave until he finds captain john's treasure island that's final
and until that day comes we're sticking with him
you just let it all out don't be afraid to cry we all feel the same way
you just let it all out of this place you guys can use a life raft or something what how could you
this is captain buggy's ship not yours well i don't see buggy anywhere do you no i guess not
i'm not gonna march to death's doorstep and as for this ship i won't let you waste it
those conditions aside if you want to rescue buggy on your own then i won't stop you
you can't scare us who cares about sea kings or government prisons we'll rescue buggy for sure right
but i'll be frank boys you're not going to last five minutes in those waters
captain thank you for everything but this is farewell your dream will live on in our hearts at least
have a peaceful execution maybe it'll be fun see you in the next one captain
i feel your grief richie there's no shame in sadness
this is momonga marine code g100660 we'll be sailing on the current shortly so prepare to open the gate
the navy ship luffy and hancock are on is approaching the tub current used exclusively by the navy to
travel between three of the world government's central facilities
is
uh
Ah! Ah! Ah! Just let me die!
Hey, new guy.
You don't get to eat until you pay your respects to the cell leader. Them's the rules around here.
What? You want me to do a little curtsy every time I take a bite out of something? Screw you.
No. I want you to give your food to the boss so I don't have to pound your sorry brains in.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Ah! Ah! Yeah!
You get it now?
Now...
Yeah!
Hey, buddy.
No need to get men down to shape, it was just a little disagreement!
I just got here, man! I'm not even on death row!
Don't let me out!
Four and a half days have passed since Luffy and Hancock left the maiden island of Amazon
Lily.
Vice Admiral, we have arrived at Impel Down.
Hurry and open the gate!
Aye aye, sir!
All right, Impel Down, this is it!
I'm sorry, sir. It's just that we're a bit late, sir.
The headwinds delayed us, but we contacted the prison.
We are late! Damn!
Call Hancock and quickly!
Sir! Uh, Lady Hancock, ma'am! We've arrived!
One moment!
This is crazy! They got more ships here than they did for the buster call!
Considering the circumstances, this might be the most dangerous place in the world right now.
But wait, you've seen a buster call? It's amazing you survived!
I've heard it said that they're quite terrifying.
The strongest military action the navy is authorized to take.
An all-out attack from five vice admirals with a fleet of ten vessels.
Ace is here? You're sure?
Yes, although I imagine he's deep under water.
Hurry! Step inside my cloak.
Ace is here.
Welcome to Impel Down, Vice Admiral Momonga!
Oh, she's so hearty!
Yep, she sure is. She's the best in the world.
Beauty is power. She's the queen.
A thousand volts? No! It's like ten thousand!
Train to the heart, baby!
These men are an affront to my poor ears, Momonga.
May I please turn them to stone?
I would rather you not.
I dare say you've embarrassed the marines enough for one lifetime.
Hey, are we inside now?
Not yet. Stay calm, please.
Now, about that condition of yours.
Before aiding in his execution, you wanted to meet Portgus D. Ace, correct?
Let me warn you once more that, warlord or not, as a pirate, you're not welcome here.
As a result, before you enter, they will perform a full-body search.
They will also require you to wear Sea Prism Stone handcuffs inside.
They have to ensure that you don't launch any ill-fated attempts at rescuing Ace
or any other prisoners.
Luffy, they're doing a body check.
We'll figure something out. Don't worry.
Very well. Go.
What? Buggy the Clown?
You said he's missing? And what's his power?
Excuse me, sir, but Vice Admiral Momonga and Empress Hancock of the Seven Warlords have arrived.
Right. I'll greet them.
She's great! Wait, I mean, somebody! Open the gate!
Come on! Quick! Let her in!
All right. This is it.
Careful in there! We love you, Hancock! Have a nice visit!
Silence, imbeciles!
Aw, she's so sexy when she's angry!
Oh, let me out!
I'm dying in here!
Nobody deserves this!
It certainly lives up to its reputation. This is quite hellish indeed.
We've made it this far, but I fear the worst is ahead of us.
Welcome to my prison, Impel Town.
Oops, jumped the gun there. It's not, well, exactly mine just yet. I'm the Vice Warden here,
Hannibal, well, for now at least. It's a pleasure to meet you, Vice Admiral.
Likewise.
We've been expecting you. Ah, and this must be the Pirate Empress. My Pirate Empress, perhaps?
Oopsie, jumped the gun again. That's a bit ambitious, I suppose.
The dumbass warden is... oopsie, not what I meant. The perfectly competent warden,
Magellan, is waiting in his office on level four. He said he would like to meet with you.
Our vice manager of the jail here, Miss Domino, will be more than happy to guide you there.
It seems you're in a rush, Empress, so allow me to get this unpleasantness out of the way.
If you follow me, we'll conduct our body search and begin the tour.
If you were a new prisoner, we would have you enter the cell over there,
strip off all your clothes, and push you into an iron pot filled with boiling water.
We call it Hell's Hot Tub. It's a baptism and sanitation solution all in one.
Very economical, I think. We have quite a number of celebrity prisoners, by the way.
As you know, Fire Fist Ace showed up recently, but that's not all.
Jinbei of the Seven Wardlords is a new addition, and the former warlord Crocodile has made his
residence here for a while now. For the record, both are model prisoners that didn't bat an eye at their
little baptism. And don't worry, we search our visitors in a private room, after you.
Before we start, could you please take off your cloak? It would be far too easy for you to hide
something inside there. So I'm afraid you'll have to leave it behind. Don't mistake our thoroughness
for mistrust. We simply have a reputation we would like to uphold. And as you can see on the wall here,
we have surveillance transponder snails all over the prison. Their video footage is monitored in one
of several security rooms. Whoa! So that's the pirate empress? I heard she was hot, but like, wow!
Come on, snails! Daddy needs a close-up! Zoom in! Zoom in!
Zys-a-pry-sum in! Zoom in! Zoom in! Zoom in! Zoom in! Zoom in! Zoom in! Zoom in! Zoom in! Zoom in! Zoom
vent terminar!
Oh, and don't forget these. Keep in mind that they're Sea Prismstone.
You call me a visitor here, not a prisoner. Then you put me in those?
Transcription by CastingWords
Countdown to Ace's execution, 33 hours.
Luffy splits up from Hancock and infiltrates Impel Down on his own.
Although he's able to elude the watchful eyes of security for a time, reaching Ace seems all but impossible.
Then for better or worse, a certain red-nosed criminal appears.
On the next One Piece, a reunion in hell, the man who ate the chop-chop fruit, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!